PAVLO LYTVYNENKO

Full Stack Engineer

DETAILS

EMAIL

viburnumbox@gmail.com

LINKS

Linkedin

Github

SKILLS

React

Redux

Typescript

Node

Webpack

Unix

HOBBIES

I like to learn unix-like systems, and create the most efficient workflow using such tools like: tiling window managers, terminal emulators, vim-like key bindings etc.

PROFILE

Front-end developer with 3+ years of experience

Participated in various projects of varying complexity, maintaining existing and designing / implementing new functionality. I Consider my main task to be writing such a project architecture that will ensure a quick solution to business tasks while maintaining the scalability and readability of the code

Currently, in the team, I am responsible for the frontend and part of the backend functionality (golang microservice), support and configure aws ec2 instance. I am developing towards the position of full-stack web developer

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Front End developer, Agiliway

Lviv

Aug 2021 — Present

Work with react / redux / typescript stack. Creating of multimedia functionality using browser APIs for working with camera, microphone, screen sharing etc.

Wordpress developer, Puzzle studio

Jun 2019 — Aug 2022

Developing custom themes and plugins from scratch. Creation of high-quality blogs and eCommerce solutions using woocommerce, acf, barba-js etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Chernivtsi National University

Chernivtsi

Jan 2012 — Jan 2016